societynmore.com 2019-05-25

# Online Society Management | Accounting & Billing Software | Societynmore

**                                                                              PRIVACY AND DATA CONFIDENTIALITY POLICY**

Protecting your privacy is very important to us, thus we have developed this privacy and data confidentiality policy (hereinafter referred to as Privacy policy) to protect your personal information and keep it confidential.

This Privacy policy applies to all the services and websites offered by Remindnmore Info.com Pvt Ltd. and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (hereinafter referred to as Societynmore).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.societynmore.com/contact-us.php) through our website or you can email us at – info@societynmore.com

**Collection of information**

Societynmore collects personal information when you register with us, when you use Societynmore’s and its partner’s  products or services, visit website/s and proprietary portals, when you enter promotions or sweepstakes and at all the places owned or controlled by Societynmore and its partners. Societynmore may combine your information that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register, we ask for your personal information including but not limited to your name, email address, birth date, gender, pin code, occupation, industry, personal interests, etc. For some financial products and services, we may also ask for your address, PAN number, information about your assets, and other relevant financial information.

Once you register with Societynmore and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Societynmore collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including the information about your use of financial products and services that we and/or our business partners offer.

Societynmore automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information and pages you request.

Societynmore is the sole owner of the information collected on this and other sites maintained and owned by Societynmore. We at Societynmore believe in keeping our users’ personal data private and confidential. In compliance with the law, Societynmore will not share information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes unless expressly asked to do so.

**Using Facebook/Twitter data**

If you decide you would like to sign-up with Societynmore services using the _‘Sign in with Facebook/Twitter’_ option, then you are giving Societynmore access to –

Your  _‘basic account information’ (including your date of birth)_  and  _‘public information’_  as defined by Facebook and Twitter respectively.

You authorize Societynmore to access your data/information (including _‘basic account information’_ and _‘public information’_ ) from Facebook/Twitter, even when you are not online on Societynmore platform.

You authorize Societynmore to pull posts from your Facebook/Twitter account.

You authorize Societynmore to push posts to your Facebook/Twitter account.

Societynmore undertakes not to transmit and/or transfer your Facebook/Twitter _‘data/information’_ to any other third party. In this regard we undertake to adhere to the policies as set out by Facebook/Twitter.

You authorize Societynmore to access _‘your information’_ as available on Facebook/Twitter for the purposes of enhancing our user experience on our platform/website.

In relation to any queries/feedback regarding the _‘Sign in with Facebook/Twitter’_ feature on our website, the users can contact us at info@societynmore.com.

In the event of any conflict between the privacy policy of Societynmore and the privacy policy of Facebook/Twitter, the privacy policy of Societynmore shall prevail.

**Children**

We at Societynmore are extremely careful about safety of children below 18 years of age. Keeping in view legal provisions and social impact, we advise that when a child under age 18 attempts to register with Societynmore, we ask that he or she shall have a parent or guardian accompanying him or her while using our services.

Societynmore will not contact children under age 18 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission.

Societynmore does not ask a child under age 18 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion.

**Sharing of Data**

Societynmore do not rent, sell, or share your personal information with other people or nonaffiliated parties except to provide products or services you’ve requested and in the limited circumstances described below –

**(1)**       **Your Consent:**  We may share or disclose your information at your direction, such as when you authorize a third-party web client or application to access your account.

**(2)**       **Service Providers:**  We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.

**(3)**       **Complying with Law and Law Enforcement Agencies** : Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is necessary to share information in order to comply with the law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Societynmore’s rights or property.

**(4)**       **Business Transfers:**  We may share or disclose your information with other Societynmore businesses and associates, as needed in connection with the transfer of any business information/assets. We may also do so with our agents, affiliates or contractors who use it on behalf of or in connection with their relationship with us.

**(5)**       **Mergers and Acquisition:**  We may share/transfer your information if Societynmore is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, A Societynmore will notify you beforehand about such transfer. In such case, your information becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Cookies**

Societynmore may set and access its cookies on your computer. Societynmore lets other companies show advertisements on its pages and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Societynmore’s cookies.

Societynmore uses web beacons to access its cookies inside and outside our network of websites and in connection with Societynmore products and services.

**Your Ability to edit and delete your account information and preferences (opt-in-opt-out)**

You can edit your Societynmore Account Information, including your preferences, at any time.

New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

Certain communications from Societynmore, such as service announcements, administrative messages, etc. are considered part of Societynmore membership and you may not opt out of receiving them.

The Users who are members of any Society and are consequently part of our Society Management service shall not be able to delete their account as long as they are part of any Society managed by us. The other Users can email us at [info@societynmore.com](mailto:info@remindnmore.com) for account deletion.

**Confidentiality and Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.

We limit access to our employees to your personal information who we reasonably believe need not to come in contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the Government regulations to protect personal your information.

Your Societynmore Account Information is password-protected. In certain areas, Socnmore uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy policy**

Societynmore may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Societynmore account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Effective:**  1st of August, 2013

**Facebook**  –

**Twitter –**
